windsorbrokers.biz 2012-10-31

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Windsor Brokers Ltd. (the "Company" "we", "our" or "us") and/or its affiliates respect rights of individuals to privacy and therefore treat the privacy with utmost importance.

**Collecting Information**

In order to receive more information, register for a demo account, open a trading account with us, you are requested to complete the Application Form. By completing the Application Form and providing your personal information, you enable us to evaluate the application and comply with laws and regulations governing the provision of financial services.

The information may be used for providing you with information we believe may be useful; about the updated or new products, services, technical issues, surveys etc.

**Confidentiality**

Any personal information is treated as confidential and may be shared only within the Company, by its employees and affiliates for business purposes, as permitted by the applicable law. The information may be disclosed to third parties, such as the Companies Partners, Affiliates and Business Introducers for business purposes only, such as, but not limited to, servicing Client accounts and informing Clients about new products and services. Our company partners, affiliates, and Business Introducers maintain the privacy of your information to the same extent Windsor does in accordance with the policy.  Information may also be provided to non-affiliated companies, providing professional, legal, accounting advises and, but not limited to, companies providing statistical services to the Company for improving the Company's website, and information may further be disclosed if requested by law and/regulatory authorities.

Non-affiliated companies that assist Windsor in providing services to you are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it and to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes that Windsor orders. Windsor will at no time whatsoever sell personal information to any third party.

Under limited circumstances, we may disclose your personal information to third parties as in a good faith as permitted by, or in order to comply with, applicable laws and regulations. The personal information may be disclosed to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies demanding evidence or other official requests, and as may be required in order to protect the Company's rights or property.

We DO Share personally identifiable information with Third Parties solely for statistical purposes and in an effort to better improve the Company's marketing and advertising activity.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small text files that are transferred from a web server and stored on the hard drive of your computer. The information collected and stored by cookies is linked to any personally identifiable information you have submitted while on this site.

We use both, session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file.

Website tracking systems may also collect data relating to the pages you have accessed, the frequency of visits etc.

**Changes in this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, without prior notice, by publishing changes on this website. It is recommended that this website is review frequently.
